const myQuestions = [
  {
    question: "When did Stan Lee join Marvel Comics?",
    answers: ["1939", "1936", "1940", "1934"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question:
      "Ant-Man has had a number of incarnations. Which of these was his first?",
    answers: ["Scott Lang", "Eric O Grady", "Mick Taylor", "Hank Pym"],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Avenger known as Hawkeye's real name?",
    answers: [
      "Clint Barton",
      "Conner Barren",
      "Hunter Smith",
      "Travis Anderson"
    ],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am one of Marvel's most peculiar heroes. I am an animal you will most likely find on a farm. One of my weirdest foes has a bell for a head. Who am I?",
    answers: [
      "Steven the Sheep",
      "Rocket the Raccoon",
      "Howard the Duck",
      "Krypto the Superdog"
    ],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question:
      "In what Marvel Comics title did the Silver Surfer first start soaring the skies?",
    answers: [
      "Fantastic Four",
      "The Avengers: Infinity Wars",
      "Spider-Man",
      "The Silver Server"
    ],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question:
      "What job did Captain America, Steve Rogers, used to have when he wasn't being a hero?",
    answers: ["Architect", "Writer", "Cashier", "Zookeeper"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am Marvel's Sorcerer Supreme. Even though I did not join the Avengers, I helped found its sister team, the Defenders. My main enemies are demons and occult beings. I am usually guided by an 'Ancient One.' Who am I?",
    answers: ["Doctor Abnormal", "Doctor Strange", "Mr. Manhattan", "Superman"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Peter Parker?",
    answers: ["Some Guy", "Spider-Man", "Captain America", "Mr. Fantastic"],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Where is the home of the Fantastic Four?",
    answers: ["New York City", "Minneapolis", "Atlanta", "Washington DC"],
    correct: 0
  },
  {
    question: "When did Stan Lee pass away?",
    answers: [
      "November 15,2019",
      "Nobember 20, 2018",
      "November 12, 2018",
      "November 12, 2019"
    ],
    correct: 2
  }
];
